[ED.
I've made glass.
I have it.
My cup in this one.
The sun in the west
The sun is so bright in the west.
It's been a while
Tanabata beach
You're here.
Aren't you near Kokusai-mura?
That's where we spent a lot of time.
Memories.
Yeah, I guess so.
Bye.
Yeah!
It was kind of like having a lot of people over for the holidays, wasn't it?
Pimples.
I'll introduce you. I'm already in the style of exposing it.
You don't like giant pimples.
I already know what's causing it.
What is it?
I know there's something wrong with it.
That's why
You said you wouldn't lose.
When we were shooting the music video.
We had a lot of snacks.
Right.
There's a lot of waiting time when you're shooting a music video.
So we had a lot of snacks.
And it was cold, so it was even colder.
Everyone ate a lot.
Yeah, we were saving up energy.
And then it was all gone.
Yeah, and then this happened.
That's what happens when you eat that much.
That's right.
We're on tour now.
Yes, we are.
We're on a national tour.
Yes, sir.
We will never be defeated!
I will not be defeated by acne
Yes, sir.
I can't lose to acne!
So...
I wonder where they're turning now.
By the time this goes up...
I'm guessing Nagoya and Osaka...
I'm sure they've already been to Nagoya and Osaka.
Maybe he's already been to those places.
I haven't been to Fukuoka yet.
I'm really looking forward to going to Hokkaido.
I like Hokkaido. It's nice there.
We'll see how the tour goes... there's a lot of songs, and we'll be on the road all the time.
It's a physical challenge, so maybe you won't have time to eat the local delicacies.
It's not impossible that I might not have the energy to eat the local delicacies.
But I'd like to enjoy it as much as possible.
Even if it's not in your hometown, there are people who are willing to go with you to various places.
It's like traveling together.
But, you know, there's nothing more precious than to have a person you admire come to your place.
I'm so happy. I wonder if she took the escalator there.
You get off the bullet train and go down the escalator there.
I wonder if he saw our escalator.
Yes, yes, yes...
or, "Oh, wait, I'm sure he used this escalator.
That's all there is to it.
I understand.
It makes me happy.
So when I think that I'm used to being in that position... it's awful.
I'm looking forward to it.
The last day of the show was at LINE CUBE Shibuya.
It's my first time, right?
First time, first time. I've never been there before.
So it's like that.
But you already know the set list.
Well, what's that?
We know the set list for the whole show. So we're looking forward to it.
But...
I don't know what's going to happen by this time, but there will be more and more new songs.
Yeah, new songs are coming out.
We've been preparing the new songs for quite a while.
It's a long time ago, isn't it? Really, really long time ago.
It's really... Summer's over.
After the summer tour, you've been working on it.
A lot of things have been going on behind the scenes.
We're surprisingly in tune with each other.
I want to be a plug rider. I have a phobia of public places.
I'm the only one who would do it. I'd love to go ballooning.
I'd love to go ballooning, but I'm not into plug gliding or skydiving.
I really, really want to do it, but absolutely no, you can't fly in the air in the flesh.
Not many girls have said they'd like to go skydiving.
Of course not. I don't think there are that many.
Not at all.
What? Because it's scary!
At any rate, I really want to try paragliding.
Is there anything you'd like to do?
If there was a "Let's make your dream come true" corner, what would you want your dream to come true?
Let's see...
For example, I'd like to fly in the sky.
What?
What? Wait a minute.
Just a minute.
I want to be surrounded by capybaras.
Oh, that's good. That's so good.
That's so good. That's so good.
I want to play with capybaras.
But, you know, from a viewer's point of view...
It's just a reward for me.
That's great!
Then you can have your own private life.
When it comes to this project...
It's a project that works
and interesting
And interesting.
Sky-living, for example, is really worth seeing, isn't it?
Oh, you're right.
I see.
I tried the circus.
Wow!
Flying trapeze.
It's a long-term project, isn't it?
That's for sure.
Then have her go practice.
Like Karen's dolphins.
Have her go every day.
Flying trapeze.
The first time I saw the circus, I was really impressed.
Oh, really?
Yeah, it's amazing. Agura's amazing. I've always wanted to try flying trapeze.
That's great. You should do it.
I'd love to do something athletic like that.
I can't wait to play baseball on the Northeast Line.
I want someone to bring nine players to play against.
Nine-man teams are hard to come by.
We can't lose to a baseball team.
We'd have to be on par with them.
You know, TV...
I think it's a staff member who can get us on the air.
Would you or I do it? I'm sure they'll do it.
I'd like to play baseball with them.
But we're too lazy to play baseball, right? I don't think so.
We can't even play ball because we can't hit it.
It's true, it's more fun to play either ball.
It's impossible to play either ball.
But that's not fun. There are people who can catch the ball.
There's a guy who can throw it.
Is that so? No? It's either you get hit or you don't.
It's a game of skill, like baseball.
That's true.I'm sure.
Yuna, I want to play tug of war with various groups.
You've been saying that for a long time.
I'm confident in tug of war.
I really think I can win in tug of war.
I want to fight even with guys.
I want to be in a tug-of-war tournament.
There's something in it for you, isn't there?
Isn't there? Somewhere.
I'm sure there is.
There's got to be something.
Gymnastics is fun, isn't it?
It's fun to watch them fight.
It's fun to watch them fight and see them do it.
So, by all means...
I'm looking for a partner!
Please contact me here.
I'll put up an errand column for you.
Drive Comparison
I like it!
But, you know... studying.
Mu wants to get his license... so when he gets his license... we'll have fun.
It would be fun to go somewhere with Mew.
What?
I can't imagine it with Mew driving.
Yeah, that's why it's fun, right? I can imagine YoonA or Rinne driving.
But a girl like Mew or Kaya driving is a gap.
But she really wants to get it. She really wants to get it.
Let's wait and see if Mew can get it.
Don't interfere too much.
Anyone can get a driver's license.
But if Karen says she'll get it, I might stop her.
You're right.
It might take a while.
Karen might be more dangerous than I am at home.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
I've been getting up about two hours before my alarm.
But you wake up early these days, don't you?
I wake up early these days.
I'm in a hurry.
The other day...
For about a day in a row, you know... when it stopped...
I woke up first.
Yeah, it's totally possible to be the first.
I was in a real hurry.
I don't know what it was, but I started getting up.
I can get up. Or maybe I'm not sleeping.
Oh, you mean the other way around?
I can't sleep because I'm anxious.
I'm not sure I'm going to wake up.
Oh, I don't know.
I'm kind of oversleeping, and I don't want to oversleep.
Oh.
No, of course that's always been the case, but...
I'm just thinking, "I don't want to oversleep.
I'd go to bed and wake up once, two hours before the alarm.
I'm like, "Wow, I can still sleep in.
But I'm already awake.
I'm waking up.
I'm still going back to sleep.
Uh...
Oh, but it's amazing.
I'm in a real hurry these days.
Ha-ha-ha.
That's my favorite.
Like that one.
Time.
What? There are times when I wonder if we missed the time.
I know, right?
I know.
That's right.
I think I'm getting the hang of it.
Oh, my God.
Really?
I used to just stop the alarm and go back to sleep.
But now I wake up when the alarm goes off.
Of course. That's what an alarm is.
What's an alarm?
You have a bunch of alarms.
So I just woke up at the last alarm.
But then I realized I was going to oversleep.
So when the alarm goes off, I make up my mind.
I'd wake up with a "hmmm" and I'd get up.
Oh, this is a natural exercise, isn't it?
No, but, you know, people who know what I'm talking about understand it.
If you're trying to wake up at the last alarm, you may be surprised to find that it's impossible.
But if you stay in bed, it's okay.
I see.
That's what I was getting at.
But isn't that a good realization?
I hope everyone notices.
So, today, I'm going to visit
Glass Design Studio in Tanabata Beach
Liko, a glass design studio in Tanabatahama
We made a combo.
It was fun!
Please look forward to the next Gundam!
Bye bye!